<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<legal2topic xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="urn:lw:names:dita:xsd:legal2topic.xsd" id="l1">
    <title>Legal information</title>
    <legal2body>
        <legal2section>
            <title>Data sheet status</title>
            <simpletable>
                <sthead>
                    <stentry><p>Document status</p></stentry>
                    <stentry><p>Product status</p></stentry>
                    <stentry><p>Definition</p></stentry>
                </sthead>
                <strow>
                    <stentry><p>Objective [short] data sheet</p></stentry>
                    <stentry><p>Development</p></stentry>
                    <stentry><p>This document contains data from the objective specification for product development.</p></stentry>
                </strow>
            </simpletable>
        </legal2section>
        <legal2section>
            <title>Definitions</title>
            <dl>
                <dlentry>
                    <dt>Draft</dt>
                    <dd><p>The document is a draft version only. The content is still under
                        internal review and subject to formal approval, which may result in
                        modifications or additions. NXP Semiconductors does not give any
                        representations or warranties as to the accuracy or completeness of
                        information included herein and shall have no liability for the consequences of
                        use of such information.</p></dd>
                </dlentry>
            </dl>
        </legal2section>
        <disclaimer2>
            <title>Disclaimer</title>
            <dl>
                <dlentry>
                    <dt>Limited warranty and liability</dt>
                    <dd>
                        <p>Information in this document is believed to
                            be accurate and reliable. However, NXP Semiconductors does not give any
                            representations or warranties, expressed or implied, as to the accuracy or
                            completeness of such information and shall have no liability for the
                            consequences of use of such information.</p>
                        <p>In no event shall NXP Semiconductors be liable for any indirect, incidental,
                            punitive, special or consequential damages (including - without limitation - lost
                            profits, lost savings, business interruption, costs related to the removal or
                            replacement of any products or rework charges) whether or not such
                            damages are based on tort (including negligence), warranty, breach of
                            contract or any other legal theory.</p>
                        <p>Notwithstanding any damages that customer might incur for any reason
                            whatsoever, NXP Semiconductors’ aggregate and cumulative liability towards
                            customer for the products described herein shall be limited in accordance
                            with the <i>Terms and conditions of commercial</i> sale of NXP Semiconductors.</p>
                    </dd>
                </dlentry>
            </dl>
        </disclaimer2>
    </legal2body>
</legal2topic>
