<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<specification2topic xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="urn:lw:names:dita:xsd:specification2topic.xsd" id="sp1">
    <title>Functional description</title>
    <specification2body>
        <p>The SA58632 is a two-channel BTL audio amplifier capable of delivering 2 × 1.5 W output
            power to an 8 Ω load at THD+N = 10 % using a 6 V power supply. It is also capable of
            delivering 2 × 2.2 W output power to an 8 Ω load at THD+N = 10 % using a 9 V power
            supply. Using the MODE pin, the device can be switched to standby and mute condition.
            The device is protected by an internal thermal shutdown protection mechanism. The gain
            can be set within a range of 6 dB to 30 dB by external feedback resistors.</p>
        <specification2section>
            <title>Power amplifier</title>
            <p>The power amplifier is a Bridge-Tied Load (BTL) amplifier with a complementary
                PNP-NPN output stage. The voltage loss on the positive supply line is the saturation
                voltage of a PNP power transistor, on the negative side the saturation voltage of an
                NPN power transistor. The total voltage loss is &lt; 1 V. With a supply voltage of 6
                V and an 8 Ω loudspeaker, an output power of 1.5 W can be delivered to the load, and
                with a 9 V supply voltage and an 8 Ω loudspeaker an output power of 2.2 W can be
                delivered.</p>
        </specification2section>
        <specification2section>
            <title>Mode select pin (MODE)</title>
            <p>The device is in Standby mode (with a very low current consumption) if the voltage at the
                MODE pin is greater than VCC − 0.5 V, or if this pin is floating. At a MODE voltage in the
                range between 1.5 V and VCC − 1.5 V the amplifier is in a mute condition. The mute
                condition is useful to suppress plop noise at the output, caused by charging of the input
                capacitor. The device is in Active mode if the MODE pin is grounded or less than 0.5 V
                (see Figure 6).</p>
        </specification2section>
        <specification2section>
            <title>BTL/SE output configuration</title>
            <p>To invoke the BTL configuration (see Figure 3), the BTL/SE pin is taken to logic HIGH or
                not connected. The output differentially drives the speakers, so there is no need for
                coupling capacitors. The headphone can be connected to the amplifier negative outputs
                using a coupling capacitor for each channel. The headphone common ground is
                connected to the amplifier ground.</p>
            <p>To invoke the Single-Ended (SE) configuration (see Figure 15), the BTL/SE pin is taken to
                logic LOW or connected to ground. The positive outputs are muted with a DC level of
                0.5VCC. Using a coupling capacitor for each channel, speakers can be connected to the
                amplifier negative outputs. The speaker common ground is connected to the amplifier
                ground. Headphones can be connected to the negative outputs without using output
                coupling capacitors. The headphone common ground pin is connected to one of the
                amplifier positive output pins.</p>
        </specification2section>
    </specification2body>
</specification2topic>
